

# **GAURI KAUSHIK**

#### SYMBIOSIS CENTRE FOR MEDIA AND COMMUNICATION

#### **Personal Dossier**

I'm a 19-year-old media student who enjoys challenges and has an ardent desire for knowledge and experience. I've enjoyed and genuinely loved the entire process of brainstorming that goes into marketing by working for my school fest over the years.

# **Work Experience**

#### **Campus Ambassador**

IIT DELHI| February 2020-Present

Promoting IIT Delhi's fest on various social media platforms.

#### **Campus Ambassador**

Delhi Technology University(DTU)| March 2020-May 2020

- -Responsible for collecting required resources
- -Promoting DTU on social media

### **Marketing Intern**

Brand Engineerz October 2019-December 2019

- Content Creation for social media

## **Professional Skills**

Leadership Skills

- -Team Work
- -Organization
- -Time Management
- -Fluent in two languages (English and Hindi)

## **Areas of Expertise**

- -Blogging
- -Web Analytics
- -Search Engine Optimisation (SEO)
- -Online Advertising
- -Social Media Marketing
- -Accountancy

# **Education History**

# Symbiosis Centre For Media and Communication, Pune

BA Mass Communication, Major in Advertising

- Second Year
- GPA 7.62/10
- Head of Advertising Magazine

## **GEAR Innovative Intl. School, Bangalore**

Commerce with Mass Media(CBSE)

- Class of 2019
- Percentage 91%
- Secured 1st place in Accountancy, Business Studies and Mass Media in CBSE board
- House Captain

#### New Horizon Gurukul, Bangalore

- Class of 2017
- -CGPA 9/10
- -House Vice Captain

#### **Contact Details**

Mobile: +91 9686474589

Address: F-205, Purva Fountain Square, Marathahalli, Bangalore, Karnataka, 560037.

Country: India

Email: gaurikaushik20nov@gmail.com Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gauri-

kaushik-a119701a1/